<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days of Yoga</string>
    <string name="title_1">Mountain Pose (Tadasana)</string>
    <string name="description_1">The Mountain Pose, or Tadasana in Sanskrit, is a standing pose that forms the foundation for many other yoga poses. Tadasana strengthens the legs, improves posture, helps to calm the mind and improve balance.</string>
    <string name="title_2">Chair Pose (Utkatasana)</string>
    <string name="description_2">Utkatasana is a strengthening pose that targets the legs, hips, and back muscles. It requires balance, stability, and focus, making it a great pose for building overall body strength.</string>
    <string name="title_3">Standing Forward Bend (Uttanasana)</string>
    <string name="description_3">Uttanasana stretches the hamstrings, calves, and spine. It can also help to reduce stress and calm the mind.</string>
    <string name="title_4">Half Forward Bend (Ardha Uttanasana)</string>
    <string name="description_4">This gentle forward bend is a part of Sun Salutations and a great way to warm up the muscles and improve flexibility. It stretches the hamstrings and strengthens the legs and spine.</string>
    <string name="title_5">Plank Pose (Phalakasana)</string>
    <string name="description_5">The Plank Pose is a bodyweight exercise that builds strength in the arms, core, and legs. It requires balance, stability, and focus, making it a great pose for improving overall body strength and posture.</string>
    <string name="title_6">Cobra Pose (Bhujangasana)</string>
    <string name="description_6">The Cobra Pose is a back bend that strengthens the muscles in the back, opens the chest and improves posture.</string>
    <string name="title_7">Downward Facing Dog (Adho Mukha Svanasana)</string>
    <string name="description_7">Downward Dog is one of the most famous yoga posesAdho Mukha Svanasana is a staple of many yoga practices. It stretches the hamstrings, calves, and back, improving flexibility in the spine and legs while building strength in the shoulders and arms.</string>
    <string name="title_8">3-legged Downward Facing Dog</string>
    <string name="description_8">This variation of the Downward Facing Dog requires more balance, stability and flexibility. It’s a great way to strengthen the whole body and stretch legs and hips.</string>
    <string name="title_9">High Lunge/Crescent Lunge</string>
    <string name="description_9">The High Lunge, also known as the Crescent Lunge, is a pose that strengthens the legs, hips, and core while stretching the hip flexors and quadriceps.</string>
    <string name="title_10">Warrior I (Virabhadrasana I)</string>
    <string name="description_10">Warrior I is similar to Crescent Lunge but the back heel is grounded which ads more stretch to the calf, legs and hips.</string>
    <string name="title_11">Warrior II (Virabhadrasana II)</string>
    <string name="description_11">Warrior II pose, or Virabhadrasana II is a pose that strengthens the legs, hips, and core while improving balance and stability. It is a great pose for building confidence and improving focus and concentration.</string>
    <string name="title_12">Reverse Warrior (Viparita Virabhadrasana)</string>
    <string name="description_12">The Reverse Warrior is a variation of the Warrior II that focuses on stretching the side body and hips while still strengthening the lower body and improving stability.</string>
    <string name="title_13">Extended Side Angle Pose (Utthita Parsvakonasana)</string>
    <string name="description_13">Just like other standing poses, Utthita Parsvakonasana strengthens the lower body and core an also stretches the side of the body.</string>
    <string name="title_14">Triangle Pose (Trikonasana)</string>
    <string name="description_14">Triangle Pose strengthens the legs and back muscles while stretching the inner thighs, hips and hamstrings. The pose requires a good deal of balance and coordination, making it a great option for improving these skills.</string>
    <string name="title_15">Wide-Legged Standing Forward Bend (Prasarita Padottanasana)</string>
    <string name="description_15">Prasarita Padottanasana improves flexibility in the legs and spine, it stretches the back, hamstrings and inner thighs.</string>
    <string name="title_16">Tree Pose (Vrksasana)</string>
    <string name="description_16">The Tree Pose is a balance pose that strengthens the legs, hips, and core. It is a great pose for improving posture, focus, and concentration.</string>
    <string name="title_17">Child’s Pose (Balasana)</string>
    <string name="description_17">The Child’s Pose is a calming pose that relieves stress and anxiety. It is a gentle stretch for the hips, back, and legs.</string>
    <string name="title_18">Cat-Cow Stretch (Bitilasana Marjaryasana)</string>
    <string name="description_18">The Cat-Cow Stretch is a gentle spine stretch that improves flexibility and mobility in the spine, neck and shoulders. It is a great way to warm up the muscles , release tension from the muscles around the spine and improve posture.</string>
    <string name="title_19">Staff Pose (Dandasana)</string>
    <string name="description_19">Staff Pose is often used as a preparatory pose for more advanced seated postures. It strengthens the core and back and can be a gentle stretch for the hips and hamstrings.</string>
    <string name="title_20">Seated Forward Bend (Paschimottanasana)</string>
    <string name="description_20">Paschimottanasana stretches the back of the body – back, hips and legs. It also helps to calm the mind and reduce stress and anxiety.</string>
    <string name="title_21">Head to Knee Pose (Janu Sirsasana)</string>
    <string name="description_21">This yoga pose also stretches the back of the body and calms the nervous system. It can be an additional stretch on the hips and side of the body compared to the previous forward bend with two legs straight.</string>
    <string name="title_22">Seated Spinal Twist</string>
    <string name="description_22">A seated twist, this pose is great for stretching and improving the mobility of the spine and hips, and can also help to improve digestion.</string>
    <string name="title_23">Easy Pose (Sukhasana)</string>
    <string name="description_23">This simple seated pose is a good starting point for meditation and pranayama, as it promotes calmness and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="title_24">Bound Angle Pose (Baddha Konasana)</string>
    <string name="description_24">Bound Angle, also known as Butterfly, is a seated hip opener, great for stretching the inner thighs and hips.</string>
    <string name="title_25">Seated Wide Leg Forward Bend (Upavistha Konasana)</string>
    <string name="description_25">This seated forward bend stretches the hamstrings, inner thighs and hips, while also helping to calm the nervous system and relieve stress.</string>
    <string name="title_26">Garland Pose (Malasana)</string>
    <string name="description_26">Garland Pose, or yoga squat, is a great hip opener that helps to stretch the hips and groin, and improves the mobility of the lower body.</string>
    <string name="title_27">Bridge Pose (Setu Bandhasana)</string>
    <string name="description_27">Bridge pose is a simple backbend that stretches the front body and strengthens the back.</string>
    <string name="title_28">Happy Baby Pose (Ananda Balasana)</string>
    <string name="description_28">This playful pose is a gentle way to stretch the hips, lower back and inner groins, and can also help to calm the mind and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="title_29">Supine Spinal Twist (Supta Matsyendrasana)</string>
    <string name="description_29">This restorative twist is great for stretching the spine, hips and neck. It can also help to relieve lower back pain and improve digestion.</string>
    <string name="title_30">Corpse Pose (Savasana)</string>
    <string name="description_30">The ultimate relaxation pose, this lying pose helps to reduce stress and tension, improve circulation and overall relaxation.</string>
    <string name="day_s">Day %s</string>
</resources>